{
    "id": "b53a173d302146e1bc9b8549042db743",
    "title": "Comparison Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You should write …………………………… legibly.",
            "description": "The comparative indicates progress. ",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a733fdded75640cd85b088c2983bfe9e"
        },
        {
            "question": "That was the ……………………… interesting movie I have ever seen.",
            "description": "The superlative shows the highest degree. ",
            "answers": [
                "most",
                "more"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5eb559d897694d0090fbd0b9880b12cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who is the …………………………. girl in the class?",
            "description": "The superlative is used to compare a person or thing to the whole group to which that person or thing belongs.",
            "answers": [
                "prettiest",
                "pretty",
                "prettier"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2d7f67d3090c4b50b3889a464a2dab8d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not at all ………………………………… with your performance.",
            "description": "When there is no idea of comparison we use the positive adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "impressed",
                "more impressed",
                "most impressed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "52304cd42a7e40fd8307f6c093cbe8f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The children sang ……………………………..",
            "description": "When there is no idea of comparison we use the positive adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "merrily",
                "more merrily",
                "most merrily"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "32f496d8dd9345d882bdb2a84ba9324c"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I talked to her yesterday, she sounded …………………………….. than ever.",
            "description": "Use a comparative expression before than.",
            "answers": [
                "happy",
                "happier",
                "happiest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a3d73f60c4874301946e9c7afeffd21a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher encouraged them to work …………………………...",
            "description": "Either hard or harder is possible here. ",
            "answers": [
                "hard",
                "harder",
                "hardest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0b7c4f3079ea4dbeb8c536fbf8b77ad1"
        },
        {
            "question": "That was the …………………………… thing I had ever done.",
            "description": "The superlative shows the highest degree. ",
            "answers": [
                "crazy",
                "craziest",
                "crazier"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "057ffde611004eddbeb3e612082e522d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I did much ……………………………….. work today than yesterday.",
            "description": "Less is the comparative form of little.",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "little",
                "least"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f231c0b524bf453ea406b7eaa404b915"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ………………………… respect for people who ill-treat animals.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "less",
                "least"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8c7ada4bf0af43589d81e27895338b3d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She sings ……………………………. than anybody I know.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "good",
                "better",
                "best"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ba33bf5a4d69493fa938f386455de856"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is the .................................. man in the village.",
            "description": "The superlative is used to compare a person or thing to the whole group to which that person or thing belongs.",
            "answers": [
                "old",
                "older",
                "oldest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2133f212a8ad41cca67ff9a827568aa8"
        }
    ]
}